[theme music playing]
[Emilia] I like a man who knows
how to please his woman.
[Claire] You're falling for that
masked creature, Emilia.
It's the other way around.
He is falling for me.
[Erlinda] Who are you?
Let's just say I'm your boss
Jaguar's worst nightmare.
Can you please tell him to let
Diego Torillo out of prison?
I don't need to anymore.
Torillo already met up with Jaguar.
I'm running for governor
of Ardiente because
I want to change this town,
not become a puppet.
I am doing this to get justice
for my mother.
And most importantly, to free
my father from their clutches.
We have an invitation
from the rival party.
They said we shouldn't miss it.
Let me introduce you all
to your future first lady.
[cheering]
Ivy Aguas, will you marry me?
-Yes. Yes!
-Yes!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
So!
Were you surprised?!
Yes, I'm a free man now!
-Diego! Diego!
-Shut your trap! I said shut it!
-Hon! Hon! No! No. Hon.
We have to show the other side
of Diego to the people.
We should inform everyone
that Diego also receives
help from criminals like Jaguar.
Finally. This will bring about
your downfall, Diego Torillo.
One more wrong move
and I'll finish him off.
He's your dad.
He's better off as fertilizer,
just like Nimfa and soon enough, Diego.
Ouch!
Who will you meet with, Ivy?
I knew you'd come here.
-Diego! Diego!
-Shut your trap!
-Hon! Hon, no! No!
Hon…
-[door opens]
-Hon?
Hon, why are you on the floor? Come here.
Hon… That's enough.
Give me that.
-What's going on?
-Where were you?
I just had to go home
and take care of some things.
[scoffs]
Well, the last time you said that
you visited him in prison
without my knowledge.
So, did you check on him
since he just got out of jail?
Well? Did you celebrate?
Open a bottle of wine?
Hug? Kiss? Did you sleep with him?
Didn't I tell you--
I don't care what you say, got it?
Diego's nothing but trash. I'm better.
And he has no right
to be the governor of this town
because he's no Ardiente.
Arnaldo!
I'll do everything I can to stop him.
Even if that means I have to keep killing!
As long as it keeps him away from you!
[grunts]
Let go! [groans]
Arnaldo!
I said, let go!
[groaning]
Arnaldo!
[cries] Stop!
Arnaldo, please! Please, no!
[screams]
[Ivy screams] Help!
Arnaldo, please!
[Ivy] Arnaldo!
Arnaldo!
-[Ivy sobbing]
-[tense music playing]
-Ivy…
-No!
[breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
Your days are numbered, Arnaldo.
I promise you, I'll make
your life a living hell.
[sniffles, exhales]
Ivy…
What's happening to you?
[Arnaldo sobs]
You just couldn't leave your son alone.
You still have a lot of people to fool
and a lot of people to pay…
just to get Diego out.
It was going to end up that way.
He would've gotten out.
The only difference is
I got him out earlier.
It's better that way.
So that he can fight
the Ardientes properly.
Jaguar.
Now that Diego is free,
you should focus on Emilia.
Use her.
So that you can get
all of the Ardientes' wealth.
Don't worry about Emilia.
I'm already working on it.
[tense music playing]
Grandpa, about last night--
Your explanation means nothing to me.
Finish your breakfast.
We're going somewhere.
What do you mean? I have
a meeting with my staff later.
Well, it's not like you'll win
if you keep acting
like you're on the verge of a breakdown.
[Arnaldo] And he has no right
to be the governor of this town
because he's no Ardiente.
[Ivy] Arnaldo!
[Arnaldo] I'll do everything
I can to stop him.
Even if that means I have to keep killing!
As long as it keeps him away from you!
Attorney, isn't that enough evidence?
He should be in prison
for everything he's done
and for harassing Ivy!
This sounds like a confession,
but it's just a threat.
And until something bad happens to Diego,
this declaration is unfounded.
Therefore, we cannot use it as evidence.
As for harassment…
Ivy, did Arnaldo hurt you?
Arnaldo is going crazy, Attorney.
That's why he's becoming violent.
Ivy, stay away from him.
Lily, this is way too dangerous now.
We can easily ruin Arnaldo's reputation.
But that means you'll now have to face
Arnaldo and the Ardientes.
I've thought about that, Attorney.
I mean, about ruining Arnaldo.
That's always been my plan.
But then, I also know
the Ardientes fight dirty.
Just like what they did to Diego.
How they turned the tables on him.
They can do that to me too.
These are just pills to calm your nerves
and to manage your stress
and your volatile emotions.
This is your solution?
Pills.
I don't need this. I'm not crazy!
I don't have time for this, Grandpa.
I know you're not crazy, okay?
I know you're not mad, but…
Just take the medication.
Just follow the doctor, okay?
Listen to me.
You are stressed out
because Diego was freed.
You're worried and paranoid that
you might lose the election.
And to top it all off,
whether you admit it or not,
you're jealous and you're fearful
that Ivy might leave you for Diego.
[scoffs]
You think you'll last long in politics
without popping a few pills?!
Just take the darn medication!
It'll be good for you.
What will you do now, Lily?
How will we fight Arnaldo?
By force.
All my life, I've fought fairly.
But if there's one thing I've learned,
it's to learn how to play rough
to protect my loved ones.
Well, Attorney…
I think I have a better idea.
I'll continue my plans of ruining Arnaldo.
I'll drive him insane so I can
totally crush and destroy him.
Until Emilia and Julio go crazy too.
All because of what's
happening to Arnaldo.
I'll make the Ardientes go crazy.
[door opens]
[tense music playing]
[groaning]
[pants]
[breathing heavily]
What's happening?
[groans]
[tense music playing]
[hyperventilating]
What's happening?
[gasps]
Hon.
Hon, I'm sorry.
I'm-- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for what I did last night.
It won't happen again. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[labored breathing]
You'll pay for killing
Nanny Carlotta and Nimfa,
for having Diego imprisoned,
and for murdering those
innocent witnesses.
I won't kill you, but I'll destroy you.
I'll rob you of your sanity, Arnaldo.
I won't leave a shred of it.
I'll make you lose your mind…
to the point that you'll beg for death.
I… I want to apologize
for what happened last night.
It…
Hon, it's okay.
I know you're just under a lot of stress.
It's okay.
Come on, eat up.
Hon, I found this
in your bathroom last night.
It's nothing.
Ah… Grandpa thinks I need these pills,
but I really think I don't.
I'm still in control, right?
-Yes. Yes, hon.
-Yes. I am.
-If… If…
-Help yourself.
If I hurt you last night,
I swear it won't happen again.
Okay? Believe me, it won't happen again.
Yes, I believe you.
Sir Arnaldo, a package for you.
Hmm. I wonder who sent it.
Wait.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Maybe it's better
if you don't open it, hon.
Please don't open it.
It's okay. It's okay.
Are you sure?
[ominous music playing]
[tense music playing]
ARNALDO, CONFESS YOUR SINS.
YOUR CONSCIENCE WILL EAT AT YOU.
Hon!
Hon.
Somebody knows about your secrets?
-Who could it be?
-Who sent this?
Who sent it?!
Hon, hon…
I just want to know who sent it.
-No, hon, no.
-No, no, no.
-I'm just going to ask…
-Arnaldo, relax!
-Who sent me this?!
-Hon!
Hon, relax.
I just wanna know who it's from.
I'll do it, hon. I'll find out who it is.
-I just?
-No, hon. Sit down.
Relax. Just ignore it.
It's just a sick joke.
Um… Hon, you need to relax.
We have a food tasting later, okay?
I need you there, hon. I need you there.
-I just wanna know…
-Hon.
I just want to know who sent it…
Who sent it?
Shh.
[chef] This one is the red
velvet with chocolate ganache.
Then this is carrot cake, while
this is raspberry macadamia.
Okay. Thanks, chef. We'll try them out.
Hon, let's try this one first.
You taste it for us.
I have to watch my diet for my gown.
How was it?
Is it okay?
It's fine.
Chef, do you have other choices?
Can we try more?
Thank you.
Okay, this one.
[Ivy] Hmm.
[ominous music playing]
[choking]
-Yummy.
-[stammering]
Hon?
[ominous music playing]
That's not true!
[gunshots]
-Hon!
-Why?
[stammering] Are you seeing this?
-What?
-This!
What do you mean, Hon? Another customer?
Right there?!
-I'm sorry.
-What's happening?
We have to go.
-No!
-Wrap this up.
-Arnaldo, sit down.
-Wait.
No, no, no. We have to go.
No, we have to finish the food tasting.
Come on. We're running out of time.
-We're good. Come on, let's go!
-Hon.
People are watching.
Sit down. We should finish this.
Okay, what's next? This one.
[clears throat]
Wear those.
And don't take them off until
you hear Arnaldo going berserk.
-Understood?
-Yes, ma'am.
Do it properly.
Hon… Can you please behave?
-No, we should go.
-It's embarrassing--
Let… let's go. Let's go. Let's go now.
-Arnaldo, we don't have?
-I don't care! Let's go.
Let's go!
Hon…
What are you doing?!
-Are you taking a video of me?!
-What's wrong with you?
-Hon!
-You?! What's wrong with you?!
-What?!
-Is that your phone?
-Stop it!
-You gonna fight back?
-Hon! Arnaldo, relax.
It's embarrassing. Let's go. Come!
-You too?!
-Stop it!
-All you? Put your phone down!
-Arnaldo…
Hon, let's go. What's happening to you?!
Come on!
Hon! Hon.
I'm sorry… Let's go.
Get the car ready, now!
Mr. Torillo, we don't have
the information you need.
Besides, it's hard to go
against the Ardientes.
If there's one person who knows
them well, it would be me.
I lived with them before,
so I know how they act
and what their weaknesses are.
-But, sir…
-We won't drag you into this.
If you really pledged
to perform your duties,
then you will give us
the information we need.
Where can we find Arnaldo's witness?
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
-Hello, Aunt Claire!
-Emilia! What's happening?
You made me come all the way here.
Auntie, I have a surprise for you.
[chuckles]
I have a video of Diego talking to Jaguar.
And I will send it to Papa.
And when he sees it…
I'll make Papa so happy again, Auntie.
And… Of course, he needs to reward me.
He should allow me to run for a seat
in congress or for governor.
You know what, Auntie?
I cannot believe this.
Emilia is back. I am so, so back.
And I don't need to flirt
with Jaguar anymore
to get on his good side.
What do you think?
[scoffs]
Emilia…
Once your father hears about this,
he'll belittle you again.
What did he tell you?
He told you to get rid of Jaguar, right?
Not flirt with him.
Now, tell me.
How will you gain his trust? Do tell.
Aunt Claire, you came all
the way here just to scold me?
I cannot believe this, Auntie.
You know, if you just came here
to get mad at me,
please just leave. Please leave me alone.
I am just concerned, Emilia.
Auntie, bye. Leave me alone first.
[scoffs]
Use your head, Emilia.
[ominous music playing]
It's a brilliant idea.
[sighs]
[ominous music playing]
[sighs] What are you doing here?
Can you leave me alone?
[distorted voice] I know, Emilia.
Why don't you just accept my offer?
Join me and leave your father.
If you choose to come with me,
you'll have everything you want.
I will make you my queen.
If you stop helping Diego.
I know you helped him get out of prison.
Diego is the greatest hindrance
to Arnaldo's political ambitions.
The only way Arnaldo
can beat Diego is if he cheats.
That's why I want you and Diego
to be my allies.
My dream team.
So I can finally take down the Ardientes.
That's why you need
to think about my offer.
[phone ringing]
Just a minute. I have to take this.
Hello.
What?
Get out of here. You have to leave now.
Think about it, Emilia.
Arnaldo.
And this Jaguar.
[door opens]
Andres Macaraig. Can we talk to you?
We have nothing to talk about.
Stop.
I just have one question.
Did Arnaldo pay you to testify against me?
-[Ivy] This is embarrassing…
-[Arnaldo] Let's go. Let's go.
-Hon…
-I don't care!
This is not happening.
I think I'm palpitating.
This is not happening, Arnaldo!
What the hell have you been doing!?
Oh, my…
I'll talk to your doctor.
He's been giving you the wrong medication.
Emilia, there's no need.
I've talked to another doctor.
We have an appointment tomorrow.
Stay out of this. You're just his fiancée.
I'm his mother!
My opinion matters more than yours!
You know, even though
you're Arnaldo's mother,
I know that you're
planning something, Emilia.
You'll use it against Arnaldo.
You'll call him incompetent,
so you can take his place. Right?
I know you, future mother-in-law.
That's how your mind works, doesn't it?
Wow, Ivy. Really?
You know, ever since you entered
my son's life,
ever since you became his fiancée,
he's started acting crazy!
-That's enough!
-You're blaming me again.
-Hon.
I'm not crazy, okay?
I'm the mayor of this town
and soon-to-be governor.
-Nothing will change.
-You won't attend the debate!
You'll only make a fool
of yourself, Arnaldo!
Listen to me! I am still your mother!
Arnaldo!
[huffs]
[phone ringing]
Diego.
Ivy, we found Arnaldo's witness.
And he agreed to testify for us
if he has to.
That's good.
Do you know what's happening
to Arnaldo right now?
He's losing his mind.
That's why during tomorrow's debate,
the entire province will discover
what's wrong with Arnaldo.
He's gone insane.
Thank you, Ivy.
Batch, you've got this.
You're sincere and you're articulate too.
As long as Arnaldo's side
doesn't pull any stunts,
I know you'll win the debate
and the election too.
Thank you, Batch.
-It's expensive. [laughs]
-It is. Oh.
Diego, are you ready?
Born ready.
I'll reveal all of Arnaldo's secrets.
I know we can win this.
That's right. Just keep fighting. Fight!
[tender music playing]
This dress! I hate it!
It's so uncomfortable!
Emilia, have you seen
Arnaldo's video clips?
If you ask me,
I don't think he should be
making any TV appearances.
He isn't ready for the debate.
[sighs] Honestly, I really don't know.
All I know right now is
this dress doesn't suit me at all.
Oh, Raul.
You know that son of ours
never listens to us.
I don't know why I have to attend
that stupid debate, either.
I'll be forced to mingle
with everyone there again.
No.
FUEGO RESTAURANT AT 7 PM.
DON'T BE LATE.
[pensive music playing]
[phone chimes]
FUEGO RESTAURANT AT 7 PM.
DON'T BE LATE.
What's wrong?
Why are you staring like that?
Um…
Will you attend the debate later?
If I need to, I don't see why not.
Do you have anything planned
after the debate?
Not really. What about you?
Raul, can you do me a favor, please?
Can you unbutton my dress?
Do you have a date?
Well, it's for you to find out.
[camera flashes]
Ma'am, are you confident
your side win this debate?
Do you really have to ask that?
Of course, yes! We're gonna win this.
Sir, how about you?
Are you confident you'll win?
-Viva Ardiente!
-See? One hundred percent.
Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
Viva Ardiente!
Yes. Thank you.
-Viva Ardiente!
-For the new Ardiente!
Mr. Diego, can you say
you're ready for this?
I was born ready.
Are you confident you'll win this debate?
Let's just wait and see
what happens later.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, sir.
-For a new Ardiente!
-Diego Torillo!
For a new Ardiente!
[tense music playing]
In just half an hour, the two brothers,
Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo
and Diego Ardiente-Torillo,
will face off in a debate
for Poblacion Ardiente.
The two candidates for governor
will be talking about their platforms
and addressing the many issues
thrown their way.
This is the first time
the brothers will be meeting
since Diego Torillo
was released from prison
and the videos of Mayor Arnaldo
Torillo's outburst went viral.
-[cheering]
-Viva Ardiente!
Ardiente! Ardiente!
I don't think I can do this.
Hon, you can't just back out.
You'll disappoint your family.
Your supporters too.
Think about what
your grandfather's going to say.
Do you really want to disappoint him?
You can do this!
I believe in you, Arnaldo.
[supporters continue cheering]
-Thank you.
-See?
The people are waiting. Let's go?
[supporters] Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
[supporters cheering]
[phone chimes]
WE'RE HERE.
WE'RE ALL SET.
Viva Ardiente! Viva Ardiente!
-WE'RE HERE.
-WE'RE READY TOO.
Viva Ardiente!
-Miss Loring…
-Hmm?
Arnaldo's here.
He actually showed up!
Your brother.
You've got this.
[tense music playing]
Mayor, are you ready for this debate?
Of course!
Uh…
DEVIL. MURDERER.
-Mayor, are you confident?
-Excuse me.
Who did this?!
[woman] Who did that?
-Who did this?!
-Arnaldo.
-That's disrespectful.
-We don't know.
Take that down. Take that down!
Hon, relax.
-We'll take that down later.
-No, no, no.
I don't just want people to see that.
Oh, no!
-Viva Ardiente!
-Diego for the new Ardiente!
-Diego! Diego!
-Viva Ardiente!
-Diego for the new Ardiente!
-Diego! Diego!
Who did this?!
-Was it you?!
-Arnaldo!
It was you, wasn't it?!
Arnaldo!
[clamoring]
-How dare you! What?!
-Please, stop. Stop!
You've crossed the line!
Stop!
-You're all trash!
-Hon! Hon!
Stop! There are cameras!
[people speaking unintelligibly]
Just ignore them. Let it go.
-Are you okay? Relax.
-[woman] They're going to lose.
Let's go.
-Diego! Diego!
-You're going down, Mayor!
[people speaking unintelligibly]
Mayor Arnaldo Torillo was angered
after seeing one of his posters
vandalized with graffiti
depicting him as a murderer.
Now, the big question is:
Are the accusations true?
Or is it just propaganda?
Did you know that Mayor Arnaldo's
throwing a fit outside?
His huge poster got vandalized
with the word murderer on it.
-Did you know that?
-I saw it too. It's crazy.
[woman tut-tutting]
[quietly] What's happening to Arnaldo?
To be honest, Auntie, I have no idea.
He's having anxiety attacks again?
I hope not today. Of all days, Auntie.
Why does it have to be now?
Now that he's--
-There he is.
-They set it all up.
Hon, everyone's looking at you. Relax.
Are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Is he okay?
Yes. He's okay now.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
Ardiente! Ardiente! Ardiente forever!
Diego Torillo! For a new Ardiente!
Excuse me, I'll just go to the restroom.
[Ivy] Are you okay?
[Arnaldo] Yeah.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Um… I'm fine.
Actually, Ivy…
Ivy, that was a bad move, right?
I embarrassed myself.
I've already lost face.
I don't think we should continue.
Hon.
It was only normal
for you to react like that.
Anyone would react like you did
if they saw their tarpaulin
vandalized, you know.
Right?
What you did was normal.
But, more importantly, you have
to take part in this debate.
Hon, you can do this.
If ever you feel nervous
or really anxious,
just look at me, okay?
I'll be right here
to support you all the way.
You can do this, hon. You can do this.
-I can do this.
-Yes.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
I can do this.
[door opens]
[ominous music playing]
As we can see,
our mayor is suffering
from a major anxiety attack.
With that, will he still
take part in the debate or not?
Emilia, Emilia, answer your phone.
We cannot jeopardize
Arnaldo's win. Emilia?
[voice prompt] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
I feel so stupid talking to a phone!
You are so unreliable, Emilia.
Darn.
Hey, you. Don't just stand there.
Do something about this. Come on.
[clicks tongue]
Are you not allowed to talk?
[scoffs]
[groans]
[tense music playing]
[distorted voice] Emilia.
Jaguar.
Emilia, I thought you agreed
to go on a date with me?
Yes. I said tonight. But not this way.
Can you untie me? Take these off.
I'm sorry. I just got impatient, Emilia.
Watch it! Ouch.
Emilia, when was the last time
your husband took you out?
When was the last time he danced with you?
Emilia…
I really want to dance with you.
But on one condition.
What is it?
[music fades]
Jaguar, how can we dance
if I'm blindfolded?
Don't worry, Emilia.
Just hold on to me.
[tense music playing]
[music continues]
Good day, everyone.
The debate is about to start.
You may now go to the front,
Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo.
-[applause]
-Ready?
Ready.
[host] Mr. Diego Ardiente-Torillo.
[crowd cheering]
Diego Torillo! For a new Ardiente!
[tense music playing]
Ardiente! Ardiente! Ardiente forever!
-We love you, Mayor!
-Ardiente! Ardiente!
Diego Torillo! For a new Ardiente!
Ardiente! Ardiente! Ardiente Forever!
[tense music playing]
[cheering continues]
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
-Diego! Diego!
-Ardiente! Ardiente!
[cheering continues]
For a new Ardiente!
[screams]
Insolent bastards!
Make that bastard suffer!
I want Diego Torillo's head!
I know the truth about your identity.
You're Lily Cruz!
[woman] No, she isn't!
I am Lily Cruz.
No!
[theme music playing]